Guide to the College Bulletins 1902-1932
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
- Bound Volumes In History of OSU Book Collection, 1902-1932; Series 3
  - Volume of Bulletins 352-377
    - Teaching Industrial Arts, 1921
    - Summer Session, 1921
    - Service Departments, 1921
    - Training for the Vocations, 1921
    - For the Private Use of the high School Superintendent in Connection with the Cash, 1921
    - School of Vocational Education, 1921
    - Halls of Residence for Women; Rules and Regulations, 1921
    - Institutional Management, 1921
    - School of Music, 1921
    - History of Military Department, 1921
    - Moving Picture Reels Folder, 1921
    - Courses of Instruction, 1921
    - Winter Short Courses, 1921
    - Little Sketches of OAC I Engineering Folder, 1922
    - Summer Session Advance Announcement, 1922
      June 19 - July 20
    - Homemakers' Conference Program and Exhibits, 1922
      March 20-25
    - Preliminary Announcement, Summer Session, 1922
      June 19- June 29
    - List of Official Publications of the Oregon Agricultural College, 1922
    - The Campus, 1922
    - Little Sketch of OAC II Student Self-Support Folder, 1922
    - Courses of Instruction, 1922
    - Winter Short Courses Folder, 1922
    - Second Annual Canner's School, 1922
    - Summer Session Advance Announcement, 1922
      June 19- July 29
    - Preliminary Announcement, Summer Session, 1923
  - Volume of Bulletins 378-389
    - College and State, 1923
    - OAC Business Show, 1923
    - Summer Session, 1923
    - School of Commerce, 1923
    - The College Girl at OAC, 1923
    - Oregon State School of Mines, 1923
    - Short Course in Dairy Manufacturing, Herdsman's and Cow Testers Course, 1923
    - Winter Short Courses Folder, 386
    - Short Course in Farm Mechanics, 1923
    - Third Annual Canners' School, 1923
    - The Booklet of the Summer Session with Supplement, 1923
  - Volume of Bulletins 390-399
    - OAC Educational Exposition, 1924
    - Course of Instruction, 1924
    - School of Forestry OAC, 1924
    - Report of the Oregon Agricultural Economic Conference, 1924
    - Summer Session, 1924
    - School of Music, 1924
    - Speech Training for Citizenship, 1924
    - Winter Short Courses with Supplements, 1924
  - Volume of Bulletins 400-409
    - The Booklet of Summer Session, 1924
      With Supplements
    - OAC Educational Exposition, 1925
    - School of Agriculture, 1925
    - Student Loan Fund, 1925
    - Admission to OAC, 1925
    - Choosing Your Life Work, 1925
    - School of Agriculture, 1925
    - Winter Short Courses Dairy Manufacturing, 1925
    - Fifth Annual Canners' School, 1925
  - Volume of Bulletins 410-420
    - Admission to OAC, 1925
    - The Booklet of the Summer Session, 1925
    - Business and Industry, 1925
    - Preliminary Announcement Summer Session, 1926
    - OAC Summer Session Program for Athlectic Coaches, 1926
    - Science for Service, 1926
    - Special Courses for Commerce Teachers, Summer Session, 1926
  - Volume of Bulletins 421-432
    - Winter Short Courses Dairy Manufacturing, 1926
    - Training for Modern home making, 1926
    - The Booklet of Summer Session, 1926
    - Sixth Annual Canner's School, 1926
    - Biennial Report of the Board of Regents 1924-1926, 1927
    - Preliminary Announcment Summer Session, 1927
  - Volume of Bulletins 433-446
    - Winter Short Courses, 1927
    - Seventh Annual Canners' School, 1927
    - Methods of Live Line Insulator Testing and Results of Test with Different Instruments, 1927
    - Preliminary Announcement Summer Session, 1928
    - Summer Study in a Vacation Setting, 1928
  - Volume of Bulletins 447-458
    - Biennial Reports of Board of Regents, 1928
    - Short Course Grading School, 1928
    - Announcing Eighth Annual Canners' School, 1928
    - The Booklet of the Summer Session, 1929
    - Agricultural Engineering Department Announcers a Power Farming, 1929
    - Preliminary Annoucement Summer Session, 1929
  - Volume of Bulletins 459-470
    - Ninth Annual Canners' School, 1929
    - Two-week Short Course in Buttermaking, 1929
    - The Booklet of the Summer Session, 1930
    - Occupations for the Agriculturally Trained; A Vocational Guidance Booklet, 1930
    - There are Giants on the Earth in These Days, 1930
    - Handbook of Intramural Sports, 1930
  - Volume of Bulletins 471-483
    - Preliminary Announcement Summer Session, 1931
    - The Student Loan Fund, 1931
    - Entrance Information, 1931
    - The Booklet of the Summer Session, 1931
    - Combined Butter and Ice Cream Makers' Convention and Short Course, 1932
      Supplement: School ofor Rural Electric Service Men
    - Preliminary Announcement Summer Session, 1932
- Microfilmed Bulletins, 1902-1932; Series 4
  Series 4 consists of 9 reels of microfilmed versions of the College Bulletins made by the former University Archives in the 1960s or 1970s.
  - Bulletins 1 thru 30 (Reel 1)
    Ends with page 282 of Bulletin no. 30.
  - Bulletins 30 thru 75 (Reel 2)
    Begins with page 282 of Bulletin no. 30 and ends with page 257 of Bulletin no. 75.
  - Bulletins 75 thru 161 (Reel 3)
    Begins with page 258 of Bulletin no. 75.
  - Bulletins 162 thru 238 (Reel 4)
  - Bulletins 239 thru 312 (Reel 5)
    Ends with page 122 of Bulletin no. 312.
  - Bulletins 312 thru 357 (Reel 6)
    Begins with page 123 of Bulletin no. 312.
  - Bulletins 358 thru 405 (Reel 7)
    Ends with page 329 of Bulletin no. 405.
  - Bulletins 405 thru 447 (Reel 8)
    Begins with page 330 of Bulletin no. 405 and ends with page 161 of Bulletin no. 447.
  - Bulletins 447 thru 483 (Reel 9)
    Begins with page 162 of Bulletin no. 447.